forevernew.com.au 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Forever New

Forever New Clothing Pty Limited (ABN 11 118 100 100) trading as Forever New ( **Forever  New**) is committed to protecting the privacy of everyone who shops or interacts with us. This policy sets out our commitment to you on privacy.

Forever New abides by the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the _Privacy Act_ 1988 (Cth).

Forever New may collect personal information about you in store, online through our websites and using our Forever New social media accounts, apps and pages. By providing your personal information to Forever New and by using our website or joining our loyalty programs, you are consenting to Forever New collecting your personal information and using it in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Collecting personal information**

Forever New may collect personal information from you including your name, address, age, date of birth, phone and other contact details, occupation, email address, merchandise information, method of payment and any other information you provide to us. Forever New may also collect transaction information relating to your purchases with Forever New and your preferences.

Forever New collects personal information in the normal course of providing goods and services to you. These goods and services include:

  * Providing information in store;
  * Processing online purchases and payments;
  * Registering an online account;
  * Registering a loyalty account;
  * When you contact Forever New customer service;
  * By instore CCTV;
  * Processing credit card purchases;
  * Purchases and arranging product holds
  * Deliveries of purchases (including Click and Collect and Store to Door, where available);
  * Using Forever New social media accounts, pages and apps;
  * Processing gift card, PayPal and Zip purchases;
  * Entering competitions;
  * Using of social media accounts, apps and pages and log-ins (which may be hosted by third parties);
  * Recording customer accident details;
  * Processing refunds; and
  * Signing up to receive Forever New email marketing communications.

If you do not provide us with this information then Forever New may not be able to provide any services you may have requested.

Forever New may also collect personal information for recruitment and employment purposes, for trade references or other contractual arrangements. Your personal information will be held by Forever New.

**Why do we collect your personal information?**

We collect personal information as detailed above, which we may use to:

  * Process and complete transactions;
  * respond to your questions;
  * provide you with information about our products, services and offers;
  * conduct loyalty programs; competitions and promotions;
  * comply with any applicable legal obligations;
  * improve our website, products, services and offers

We may also use personal information to customise our services, to provide relevant consumer information and to provide marketing and re-marketing communications across Forever New sites, properties, stores and marketing channels.

**Use of your personal information**

In most circumstances personal information will be collected directly from you. Forever New may use your personal information to keep you up to date with Forever New’s product ranges, specials, promotions and offers that you may be interested in including for direct marketing and to develop new product ranges and services that meet your needs. Specifically, you authorise Forever New to contact you regarding your purchase and use of our online store and in relation to any Forever New membership or loyalty programs that you have joined.

Any information collected is safely and securely stored and only used for the purposes for which it was collected. We restrict access to your personal information, maintain technology products to prevent unauthorised computer access and use SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption technology when processing your financial details at our online store. The majority of personal information collected is stored within Australia, however third parties that we contract with may host this data in a cloud based system or outside Australia.

Forever New does not sell or trade any personal information collected.  We may share personal information with our related corporations and service providers, contractors who help us provide services, and/or trading partners. We often need to share your information with companies who perform parts of our service delivery. This may include:

  * Service providers e.g. IT service and software providers, systems administrators, mailing services, remarketing platforms, data analysis; and payment and order processors;
  * Companies assisting Forever New with marketing and competitions;
  * Regulatory authorities;
  * Professional advisors; and
  * Any other third party required by law.

Where we share your information, Forever New will ensure that these third parties protect your privacy in accordance with applicable laws.

Forever New may also publish some of your personal information on our website or social media pages where you have entered a competition or promotion run by Forever New.

**Unsolicited information**

Forever New may in turn receive unsolicited personal information about you from third parties or from you directly. For example, unsolicited information may come into our possession during the course of dealing with customer complaints or general enquiries. If it is clear to us that we should not have collected that information, Forever New will destroy or de-identify that information, provided it is lawful and reasonable to do so.

**Email marketing communications**

If you have registered to receive email marketing communications from Forever New we reserve the right to contact you in relation to Forever New and to create an account for you for any Forever New membership or loyalty programs. You can opt-out of receiving email marketing communications at any time. To manage your preferences or to unsubscribe, simply sign into your account, click on ‘My Preferences’ and provide your instructions. Alternatively, you may click to unsubscribe from the bottom of any of our email marketing communications.

**Disclosure of information outside the jurisdiction of collection**

Forever New may disclose personal information outside of the jurisdiction from which it was collected. In the conduct of its business, Forever New transfers to, holds or accesses information personal information from various countries including Australia, New Zealand, Canada, Singapore, India and United States. The privacy laws of those countries may not provide the same level of protection as the privacy laws of the country from which the personal information was collected. However, this does not change Forever New's commitments to safeguard your privacy and Forever New will comply with all applicable laws relating to cross-border data disclosure.

**Linking to Third-Party Websites**

When you click on links and banners on our site that take you to third-party websites, you will be subject to that third-party's privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy, Forever New is not responsible for the actions of any third-party websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by us.

**Cookies**

Our websites use "cookies" - small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalise your online browsing and shopping experience. Cookies may eliminate the need to repeatedly enter the same information, enabling us to improve the content, reliability and functionality of our websites, evaluate the effectiveness of advertising on our websites, and track website usage patterns. Accepting a cookie will not give us access to any data on your computer other than the data stored in the cookie. You may experience a loss of functionality as a result of configuring your web browser not to accept cookies. If you do not wish to allow cookies then you may elect to disable cookies, using your browser settings.

**Online Ordering security**

Forever New adheres to credit card and personal information being kept secure at all times. Therefore, to help ensure that your shopping experience is safe and secure Forever New uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL Certificates give high-security Web browsers information to clearly identify a Web site organisational identity. This encrypts all the information you send across to us including your credit card details.

**Updates to this policy**

Forever New may update its privacy policy from time to time without notice, and an updated policy will be posted on Forever New’s website.

**Right of access and correction**

You have the right to review, amend or delete your personal information that may be held by Forever New by making a request to our customer service team. We will take all reasonable steps to comply with the request, except where it is not possible for legal reasons. To protect your privacy and the privacy of others, we may need to verify your identity before we can give you access to, or change, your personal information.

**Questions – Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to access or correct your personal information or make a complaint, please contact our customer service team on [customers@forevernew.com.au](mailto:customers@forevernew.com.au "Customer Service") or phone us on 1300 720 687 for all Australian residents Monday - Friday (9am - 5pm AEDT). If you are unhappy with our responses you can contact the Office of the Australian Privacy Commissioner (see [www.oaic.gov.au](http://oaic.gov.au/)).

If you wish to not receive any communications or marketing from Forever New, you may opt-out at any time. Please use the unsubscribe button or contact the customer service team above.

_Updated September 2018_
